{
    "question": "kotak amal di masjid al aqsa menyerupai kubus, jika masing-masing kotak amal memiliki panjang rusuk 5cm maka volume ketiga kotak amal adalah...cm\u00b3\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>v1 = s\u00b3= s\u00d7s\u00d7s</p><p>   = 5\u00d75\u00d75</p><p>   =125cm\u00b3</p><p></p><p>v2= s\u00b3= s\u00d7s\u00d7s</p><p>   = 5\u00d75\u00d75</p><p>   =125cm\u00b3</p><p></p><p>v3 = s\u00b3= s\u00d7s\u00d7s</p><p>   = 5\u00d75\u00d75</p><p>   =125cm\u00b3</p><p></p><p>v1+v2+v3 = 125+125+125</p><p>                 = 375cm\u00b3</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalau salah</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "9susun-kata-campur-aduk-menjadi-kalimat-yang-baik-lama-dulu-434",
            "question": "9.Susun kata campur aduk menjadi kalimat yang baik    Lama - dulu - bagaimana - di sana - kamu - keluarga - kamu - dan\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Bagaimana kamu dan keluarga lama kamu dulu disana</p><p>Bagaimana kamu dan keluarga lama kamu di sana dulu </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>yaps, Idk whether its true or not, its just my opinion :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "13-its-still-stuck-on-my-mind-the-word-it-in-the-lyric-ab-338",
            "question": "13. \u201cIt's still stuck on my mind\"    The word \"it\" in the lyric above refers to .\r\na. day\r\nc. head\r\nb. night\r\nd. dream\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>d. dream</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>arti kata \"itu\" adalah mimpi (dream)</p><p></p><p>semoga membantu</p><p><strong>#</strong><strong>j</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>d</strong><strong>i</strong><strong>k</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>n</strong><strong>y</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>n</strong><strong>g</strong><strong>t</strong><strong>e</strong><strong>r</strong><strong>c</strong><strong>e</strong><strong>r</strong><strong>d</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>s</strong><strong>yah</strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "essays-1-give-2-examples-how-to-offering-help-2-what-is-narativ-333",
            "question": "Essays    1. Give 2 examples how to offering help\r\n2 What is \"Narative Text\r\n3. Write 2 sentences using \"should\r\n4. Name 2 examples of \"Quantifiers\"\r\n5 Give 1 sentence of \"Simple Past Tense\"\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. Hello,how could i help you?</p><p>   Hey,may i help you with something?</p><p>2.  . . .</p><p>3.You should go to bed now,Nathan.</p><p>   i think you should get some rest</p><p>4. . . .</p><p>5 . . .</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "mombe-careful-with-those-thingsthey-are-fragile-seanokay-what-150",
            "question": "Mom::Be careful with those things,they are fragile sean:okay    what does the mothet maen as,, they? \r\nA. gambar mentimun\r\nB. gambar bawang\r\nC. apel \r\nD. mie instan\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>D. Mie Instan</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>karena fragile artinya rapuh</p><p></p><p>benda yang rapuh adalah mie instan</p><p></p><p>jadikan jawaban terbaik ya </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "13-they-not-attend-the-party-yesterday-a-do-c-doing-b-did-277",
            "question": "13. They ... not attend the party yesterday    a. Do\r\nc. Doing\r\nb. Did\r\nd. Does\r\n\r\n\r\nbantu jwab ya\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>b. Did</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>B.did</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>v2 karena  sudah terjadi</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "always-j-activity-1-get-up-at-am-2-aake-his-bed-3-take-a-ba-145",
            "question": "Always    J\r\n\u2713\r\nActivity\r\n1. get up at AM\r\n2. aake his bed\r\n3 take a bath\r\n+ har's hrcaktast\r\n5. catch the bus to school\r\n6. haiclunch at school\r\nplas basketball in the aftemoon\r\n8. plas antes\r\n9. study in the evening\r\n10. go to bed at 9 PX\r\n1. How does he go to school?\r\n2. Does he like playing games?\r\n3. Where does probably he always have breakfast?\r\n4. Here are Rick's routines.\r\nThe closest meaning of the underlined word is\r\non we probably find the notice?\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. How does he go to School </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "9-gambar-disamping-di-gunakanuntuk-a-membuka-gambar-bmenyimpan-767",
            "question": "9. Gambar disamping di gunakanuntuk    a. membuka gambar\r\nb.menyimpan gambar\r\nOpen\r\nc. mencetak gambar\r\ntolong kak besok dikumpulin\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>maaf ka mana gambar nya </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf yyyyyyyyy</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>gambar mana ya\u2639\ufe0f\u2639\ufe0f\u2639\ufe0f</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "in-indonesian-april-is-season-a-wet-b-dry-c-winter-d-spri-998",
            "question": "In indonesian april is.... season    a. wet \r\nb. dry \r\nc. winter \r\nd. spring \r\n\r\nmohon dijawab kak \u200d\u2640\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>C winter kalo gk salah mohon maaf </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "B. Dry = kemarau<br><br>Penjelasan: <br>A. Wet = musim penghujan<br>B. Dry = musim kemarau<br>C. Winter = musim dingin/salju <br>D. Spring = musim semi",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-tell-the-qualities-of-the-things-and-rooms-tha-t-you-have-in-y-352",
            "question": "1. Tell the qualities of the things and rooms tha\r\n\r\nt you have in your house !.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p> </p><p></p><p> </p><p>A </p><p>1.big</p><p></p><p>2.beutiful</p><p></p><p>3.room and they are awsome</p><p></p><p>4.small</p><p></p><p>5.nice</p><p></p><p>6.clean</p><p></p><p>7.clean and big</p><p></p><p>8.is green</p><p></p><p>B</p><p></p><p>1.big</p><p></p><p>2. my home</p><p></p><p>3.is white</p><p></p><p>4.big</p><p></p><p>5.clean</p><p></p><p>6.nice</p><p></p><p>7.nice and tidy</p><p></p><p>8.small and full of grass</p><p></p><p>9.big and nice</p><p></p><p>10.full of cars and motorcycles</p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p> </p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Thing :</p><p>I have a laptop, you know what the use of a laptop is and its quality, while my bedroom is very beautiful and everything is neatly arranged</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "2-the-response-of-greeting-is-a-good-morning-b-good-night-c-192",
            "question": "2. The response of Greeting is    a. Good morning. \r\nb. Good night. \r\nc.Goodbye \r\nd See you later\r\n\r\nMohon bantuan nya kakak\r\nbesok udah harus di kumpul \u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>a.Godd morning</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>jadikan Jawaban<strong><em><u> TERBAIK</u></em></strong> ya</p><p>maaf kalau<strong><em><u> SALAH</u></em></strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}